Just for five seconds,
（岡部倫太郎(おかべりんたろう)）５秒でいい
I would like for you to draw Mr. Braun's attention,
ミスターブラウンの
注意を引き付け―
so he doesn't notice any shaking from the experiment.
実験による衝撃が起きたことを
気付かないようにしてもらいたい
Got it!
（阿万音鈴羽(あまねすずは)）分かった 分かった
そうなったら 色仕掛けだね
I'll just have to seduce him.
Want to touch it?
触ってみ？ 結構 硬いから
It's pretty firm.
It is.
（岡部）あ… 確かに
Right?
（鈴羽）でしょ？ 任せて！
Leave it to me.
You're seducing him, right?
（岡部）色仕掛けだよな？
Yup, what about it?
（鈴羽）そうだけど？
Never mind. I'm counting on you.
（岡部）まあいい… 頼むぞ
Okey-dokey.
（鈴羽）オーキードーキー！
はっ！
Now!
（鈴羽）今だ！
（岡部）助手よ 決行だ！
Assistant, go!
（天王寺裕吾(てんのうじゆうご)）何だ？
What?
おっ！ おか…
（鈴羽）あちゃー 失敗
Oh, no... I failed.
How many times do I have to tell you?
（天王寺）
てめえ 何度言ったら…
（天王寺）おお！
It stopped?
止まった？
My assistant?
助手が… いや
No...
これは まさか…
What is this?
No way!
The hell do you mean...
（天王寺）何が…
（岡部）ん？
"No way"?!
まさかだ！
（岡部）がっ！
（鈴羽･天王寺 綯(なえ)）う…
Dogma
in Event Horizon
In other words,
（牧瀬紅莉栖(まきせくりす)）つまり 偶然にも
１階の42型ブラウン管が―
～
the 42-inch CRT on the first floor
just happens to function as the lifter.
リフターの代わりとして
作用していた
So we were only able to send D-mails when the workshop was open and the TV was on...
故に 工房が営業中で―
テレビがついている時間しか
Ｄメールを送れなかった か…
That makes a lot of sense!
確かに 説明がつくわね
Don't be so loud. It hurts my head...
（岡部）大声を出すな 頭に響く
Are you okay?
（椎名(しいな)まゆり）大丈夫？
Damn Mr. Braun...
ミスターブラウンめ
暴力に訴えるとは…
I never thought you'd resort to violence.
In a way, it's your own fault.
（紅莉栖）
まあ 自業自得ともいえるけどね
You're the one who wanted to run an experiment!
実験をしたいと言ったのは
貴様だろう イテッ…
Anyway, we almost completely understand how the Phone Microwave works now.
とにかく これで電話レンジの
仕組みは ほぼ解明できた
Which means that next...
となると 次は…
we should consider physically transporting an object through time.
物理的タイムトラベルの
可能性について考えるべきだろう
Impossible.
（紅莉栖）無理
Don't dismiss it so quickly!
１秒で否定するなっ！
It's going to end up jelly, no matter what we do.
どう工夫しても
ゲル状になるのがオチよ
And how, exactly, do you fit a human into 36 bytes—
大体 人間を36バイトなんて
データに… あっ！
ああ？
Is this really the time for showing off?
こんなときに自慢か？
Why would I want to show off to you?
（紅莉栖）
あんたに自慢してどうするのよ
論文のタイトルを見て
Look at the title of my paper.
（岡部･橋田 至(はしだいたる)）んー？
"The Analysis of Nerve Pulse Signals Stored in Memory Within the Temporal Lobe."
（紅莉栖）
側頭葉に蓄積された 記憶に関する
神経パルス信号の解析
Can I get that in a language I understand?
日本語でオーケーだよ…
Essentially, it has to do with people's memories.
要するに人の記憶に関する論文
脳科学専攻なの 私…
I majored in neuroscience.
脳の中の記憶は 簡単に言うと―
Put simply, the brain stores memories as pulse signals.
パルス信号によって
蓄積されていくものなの
They're a type of electrical data.
一種の電気的なデータ
Data... You can't mean...
データ… まさか！
That's right.
そう 人間を物理的に送ることは
到底無理だけど―
Sending a human through time is impossible,
but it might be possible to send their memory data.
記憶データだけなら
送ることは可能かもしれない
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Where?
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
（橋田）どこに？
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
To the you in the past.
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
（紅莉栖）過去の自分によ
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2010/8/13 AD
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
We turn the memories into data,
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
記憶をデータ化して
Ｄメールと同じ要領で過去に送る
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Hippocampus
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
and we send them back like we did with the D-mail.
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Time Leap Machine
Basically, you're transplanting your present brain's contents into the past.
Nerve Pulse Signals --> Encode to Electric Signals
Time Leap Machine
要は 今の自分の頭の中身だけを
過去の自分に移植するわけ
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
In other words, "you" go back to the past!
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
（岡部）つまり…
過去に自分が戻る
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Overwrite Memory Data!
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Receive
Overwrite Memory Data!
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
Time Leap!
(Same as D-Mail)
Me on 2010/8/11 AD
Overwrite Memory Data!
Receive
It's more of a time leap than time travel.
（紅莉栖）
タイムトラベルというよりは
タイムリープね
It's me.
俺だ
All the lines have converged at one point.
すべての線は１本につながった
The plan will now enter its final stages.
計画は これより最終段階に入る
The goddess who rules the present...
現代を司る女神…
Begin Operation Verdandi!
オペレーションヴェルダンディの
開始だ！
Begin what now?
（橋田）ワケワカメ
（まゆり）ほえー
Explain what you're talking about a little.
少しは どういうことか
説明しなさいよ
I'm saying we're going to do that time leap you're talking about.
お前が言うタイムリープを
採用すると言っているのだ！
Begin now.
すぐに始めろ
But we'll need a lot of stuff to do it.
…って言われても 開発には
いくつか材料が必要よ
もっとも
側頭葉に蓄積されている―
Of course, we only have to read memories stored in the temporal lobe,
記憶の信号を 読み取れば
いいだけだから―
so I think I can get everything in Akiba...
アキバで そろうと思うけど…
But...
ただ…
ん？ どうした？
What's wrong?
One problem is that I don't think the Phone Microwave
（紅莉栖）
１つは電話レンジじゃ―
人間の記憶のデータを
圧縮するには―
will be able to sufficiently compress the memory data.
力不足の可能性が高いってこと
And...
それと…
What?
（岡部）何だ？
（紅莉栖）あ… いえ
Nothing.
All right.
いいわ
今 必要なパーツを書き出すから
I'll make a list of the parts I need for now.
（まゆり）まゆしぃは
難しすぎて さっぱりです
It's too hard for Mayushii to understand it at all.
Christina just explained it.
（岡部）さっきクリスティーナも
言っていたではないか
You're sending your mind, as it exists right now, to the past.
今の この自分の意識を
過去に飛ばすのだ
（まゆり）うーん
なんか おっかなそう…
Sounds scary.
Is the D-mail not good enough?
Ｄメールじゃダメなのかな？
Ｄメールは不確定要素が多すぎる
There are too many chaotic variables with the D-mail.
One message can change things you'd never expect.
（岡部）たった１通のメールで
予期せぬことが起きてしまう
But it's okay to send memories into the past?
記憶を過去に戻すのは
平気なの？
If nothing else, you can
（岡部）
少なくとも過去改変について
prevent the past from changing to some degree.
ある程度
コントロールが可能になる
You wouldn't have the entire city of Akiba changing...
アキバの町を変えてしまうような
変化は…
The city?
（まゆり）町を？
Nothing. Never mind.
（岡部）あ… いや 何でもない
Huh?
（まゆり）あれ？ でも…
But what happens to you after you send your memories?
記憶を過去に送ったあとの自分は
どうなっちゃうんだろう…
体は ここに
残ったままなんでしょ？
Your body's still here, isn't it?
Well...
（岡部）それは…
So, Mayushii is talking to Okarin now, right?
（まゆり）
それと 今 まゆしぃは―
こうやって オカリンと
お話ししてるでしょ？
（岡部）ああ…
Then, you're saying Mayushii goes back a week
（まゆり）その まゆしぃが
１週間前に飛んで―
and then relives the week, right?
１週間をやり直したとするでしょ？
What happens if she doesn't talk to Okarin this time?
そのとき オカリンと
お話ししないように―
行動したら
どうなっちゃうのかな？
I assume that you would recall that we spoke,
それは… おそらく
まゆりの中に記憶は残るが―
but the event of having spoken would be erased.
話したという事実は消える
In other words, Mayushii would remember us talking,
（まゆり）つまり まゆしぃは
お話ししたことを覚えてるのに―
but Okarin wouldn't?
オカリンは全然知らないって
ことになるの？
I'd imagine so.
（岡部）そうだな…
Then that's kind of sad.
（まゆり）だとしたらね
なんだか さみしいね
（岡部）ん… 俺が？
For me?
Nope.
（まゆり）ううん
For Mayushii.
まゆしぃが…
It's Moeka!
あっ 萌郁(もえか)さんだ
Moeka!
萌郁さーん ハハッ
（まゆり）トゥットゥルー
You look rather unhappy, Shining Finger.
（岡部）ずいぶん
浮かない顔をしているな
シャイニング･フィンガーよ
"Did you get rid of the time machine?"
タイムマシンは破棄した？
We're still using it.
まだ使ってるよ
And now, we might be able to do a time leap—
それでね 今度はタイムリープが
できるかもしれないんだって
Don't tell her about that!
（岡部）軽々しく話すな！
えーっ？
But Moeka's a lab member, too, right?
でも 萌郁さんもラボメンだよ？
She is, but...
それは そうだが
"What's a time leap?"
（岡部）タイムリープって何？
うっ うう…
文字どおりの意味だ
Just what it sounds like!
We can send memories through time.
記憶の時間跳躍を可能にする
Memories...
（桐生(きりゅう)萌郁）記憶の…
Moeka?
（まゆり）萌郁さん？
（まゆり）あ… 萌郁さーん
Moeka!
Is she okay?
大丈夫かな？
（岡部）アキバオーを
先に回ったほうが効率的か…
It would be faster to head for Akibaoo first, I guess?
Big Sis Mayuri!
（綯）まゆりお姉ちゃん
（まゆり）おおー
It's Nae!
今度は綯ちゃんだ
どうしたの？
What's wrong?
Yo.
（鈴羽）ういーっす
You're still dressed like that?
まだ その格好なのか？
（鈴羽）いやあ… 店長に１日
それでいろって怒られちゃってさ
The boss told me to stay this way all day.
You'll poison children's minds.
（岡部）
よい子には微妙に目の毒だぞ
Poison?
毒？ 毒物は持ち歩かないように
してるけど…
I'm careful never to walk around with poison.
Huh?
はあ？
Anyway, Nae said she wanted to talk to Okabe Rintarou, so we were looking for you.
あ… それより綯がさ
岡部倫太郎に 話があるって
探してたんだよ
To me?
俺に？
うん… ごめんなさい
I'm sorry!
My dad was really mean back there!
さっきは お父さんが
ひどいことして
Nae...
（まゆり）綯ちゃん
You came all this way to say that?
それを言うために
わざわざ…
What a well-trained little pet.
なんと よくできた小動物…
She's not a pet.
小動物じゃないよう
Don't worry.
案ずるな
I cause trouble for Mr. Braun all the time.
俺もミスターブラウンには
いつも迷惑をかけている
おあいこだ
We're even.
That's not like the Okabe Rintarou I know...
岡部倫太郎っぽくないねえ
（まゆり）えー？
Okarin's always like this.
オカリンは いつもこうだよ
（鈴羽）ふーん
Mayushii's gonna get going, okay?
じゃあ まゆしぃは
そろそろ行くのです
Meeting someone?
待ち合わせか？
Yup!
（まゆり）
うん レイヤーのフブキちゃん
コス渡しに行くんだ
I'm going to give the cosplayer, Fubuki, her outfit.
Come to think of it, it's almost time for Comima.
そういや そろそろコミマか
Yup.
（まゆり）うん じゃあね
鈴(すず)さんと 綯ちゃんも
Bye!
See you, Suzu and Nae!
トゥットゥルー
See you!
（綯）またねー フフフ
Okay, let's head back ourselves.
じゃあ 私らも帰ろうか
No, I need to find the parts Christina asked for.
いや 俺は まだ クリスティーナに
頼まれたパーツを探さねば
Makise Kurisu works with SERN.
（鈴羽）牧瀬紅莉栖は…
ＳＥＲＮ(セルン)に通じている
えっ？
A SERN spy?
（岡部）
ＳＥＲＮのスパイ… まさかな
No way.
Lurk...
（岡部）ぬるぽ…
（紅莉栖）がっ
...moar.
あっ
お… 音もなく近づくなんて反則よ
You can't just sneak up on me!
That's against the rules!
フフ やはり書き込んでいたのは
「アットチャンネル」か…
So, you were posting on @channel.
ちょ…
I had already realized you were an Anon a long time ago.
（岡部）貴様が生粋の
アットチャンネラーだと―
I wasn't, really...
気付いたのは ずいぶん前だ
No!
違う
There's no point in hiding it now.
（岡部）今さら隠したところで
何の意味もない
This sucks...
（紅莉栖）うつだ…
All right.
まあ いい
From now on,
これからクリスティーナには
ネラーの称号を正式に与える
I officially give you the title of Anon...
Don't give me any more weird nicknames!
（紅莉栖）これ以上
変な呼び名を付け足すな！
And please, keep this a secret!
…っていうか
内緒にしておいてよ！
Why?
（岡部）なぜだ？
You could list it on your résumé.
履歴書に堂々と書けば
いいではないか
If they knew a serious academic was posting,
趣味「アットチャンネル」と！
学者がネラーとなれば
スレの１つや２つ 立つだろう
they'd probably make a few threads about you.
Why would I care?
立ってどうするっ！
Then what? You'd sage them?
（岡部）なら ＶＩＰ(ビップ)で安価を
出すことのほうがいいというのか？
（紅莉栖）くっ
意味が分かる自分が憎い
I hate myself for understanding that last sentence.
Either way, I feel better.
（岡部）しかし 安心したぞ
I can't imagine someone who's so terrible at hiding things as a spy.
そこまで自分を隠すのが下手な
人間が スパイとは考えられんな
（紅莉栖）はあ？ 何それ？
What does that mean?
The part-time warrior said you were a SERN spy.
いや バイト戦士が
クリスティーナは―
ＳＥＲＮのスパイだと言いだして
What is that supposed to mean?
（紅莉栖）
何なのよ その言いがかり
That's impossible.
そんなわけないでしょ？
Indeed.
（岡部）全くだ
You're an agent the Organization sent,
貴様は機関から送られてきた
エージェントであり
who's had a change of heart and now works as my assistant.
今は心を入れ替え 我が助手として
働いているのだからな
That's not true either.
それも違う
So how's the work going?
それで 作業のほうは
どうなっているのだ？
Work?
作業？
The time leap.
（岡部）タイムリープだ！
パーツは すべて買ってきたぞ！
I bought all the parts.
Oh... That's right.
（紅莉栖）ああ
そうよね 作るべきよね
I should make it, shouldn't I?
I've come this far.
ここまで来たんだから…
What's this?
うん？ どういうことだ？
怖くなったのか？
You're getting scared?
That too...
（紅莉栖）それもある
I keep asking myself what'll happen if we really make it.
もし 本当にできてしまったら
どうなるんだろうって
けど それより…
But more than that...
（岡部）何だ？
What?
話しておくべきね
I should tell you...
It seems like it's half-obvious already.
どうせ こっちも
半分はバレてるみたいだし…
I can't do it here!
やっぱり ここじゃ無理
Let's go somewhere I can't see your face.
あんたの顔が
見えないとこにして…
I've got a problem with my dad...
（紅莉栖）私…
父親とのあいだに
ちょっと問題を抱えているの
So your father was struck by lightning
（岡部）では アーカンソーで
雷に打たれ―
on the grassy plains of Arkansas and fell to the dark side—
クリスティーナの父が
ダークサイドに落ちたというのは…
（紅莉栖）
ちゃかすなら もう話さない
If you're going to be a jerk, I'm not telling you.
All right. Tell me.
（岡部）分かった
聞かせてもらおう
To put it simply, my dad doesn't like me.
（紅莉栖）簡単にいうと
父に嫌われているの
ううん
No... He hates me.
憎まれてる
And not as his daughter. As a scientist, as a rival.
しかも 娘じゃなく科学者として
ライバルとして…
My dad was a physicist.
私の父は 物理学者だったの
I always liked hearing him talk about the details of his work.
私は小さいころから 父の難しい
物理学の話を聞くのが好きだった
And so, by the end of elementary school,
おかげで小学校の
高学年ぐらいで―
I could understand his papers.
父の論文が
理解できるようになったわ
And then, I started writing my own papers
そして 自分で論文を書いたり
賞をもらえるようになった
and won awards.
But I didn't care about the awards.
でも 賞なんて
どうでもよかった
I loved debating with my father.
私は父と議論ができるのが
楽しかった
We exchanged papers by email,
メールでいくつも論文をかわして
議論を深めて
and our debates got deeper.
でも…
But...
eventually, my dad stopped debating with me.
いつしか父は
私の相手をしなくなった
While I enjoyed the debates,
議論を楽しんでいるあいだに
私は論破していたの
I was also winning them.
I pointed out mistakes he'd made,
父の誤りを指摘し
父のプライドを―
and without even thinking about it, I hurt his pride.
知らずに傷つけていた
My dad started taking it out on my mom.
父は母に当たるようになった
He lost confidence and began withdrawing from his academic peers.
自信を失って 次第に学会から
見放されていった
The last time I saw him,
最後に会ったときに父は
私に こう言ったの…
he said this to me...
"Do you pity me?"
“私を哀れんでいるのか
さげすんでいるのか”
"Do you look down on me?"
"You're my daughter. How dare you?"
“娘の分際で”って
If I make a device that enables a time leap,
タイムリープできる装置を
私が作ったとしたら―
I think my dad might go insane.
父は間違いなく怒り狂うと思う
Even more than before...
今まで以上に…
So that's why you're hesitant to make it?
（岡部）それで 作るのを
ためらっていたのか
But don't worry.
（紅莉栖）でも 心配しないで
I'll end up doing it, regardless.
どうせ作るから
あんたが言うように―
私は実験 大好きだから
Just like you said, I love experimenting.
If I see a possibility, I have to investigate it.
何かを見つけたら
確かめずにはいられない
Just like my dad used to...
父がそうだったように
The time I spent with my dad...
父と私が過ごした時間が―
そうだったように…
...was like that.
（岡部）ならば すぐに！
Then we begin Operation Verdandi immediately!
オペレーションヴェルダンディに
取りかかる
There's no time to waste!
モタモタしてる暇はない！
The Organization stands at our very doorstep!
機関は すぐそこに
迫っているのだから！
（紅莉栖）結局それ？
That's your response?
Of course...
（岡部）当たり前だ
I am Hououin Kyouma.
俺は鳳凰院凶真(ほうおういんきょうま)！
It's my destiny to change the world!
世界の構造を変革する
使命がある！
（紅莉栖）
ハア… 話すんじゃなかった
I shouldn't have said anything...
And we'll help you reconcile with your dad too!
（岡部）
それと同時に和解にも行く
Where is he?
父親は 今どこにいる？
えっ？ あ… 青森だけど
H-He's in Aomori.
We'll need money to go...
（岡部）行くとなれば
資金の問題もある
When you work out the time,
時期が決まったら
早めに声をかけてくれ
tell me as soon as you can.
You can't mean you'll go with me.
（紅莉栖）…って まさか
一緒に来るつもりか？
Naturally!
当たり前だ！
お前には 我が野望のため―
I need you in peak mental condition, so you can further my ambitions!
最高の精神状態で
働いてもらわねばならん
この鳳凰院凶真が
一緒に行って―
I, Hououin Kyouma, shall accompany you,
and I shall use my masterful people skills
その場の空気を読んだ
見事な話題を提供し―
to reunite father and daughter.
親子のわだかまりを解消してやる
What the heck?
（紅莉栖）何 それ…
You're a self-proclaimed mad scientist, right?
あんた自称
マッドサイエンティストでしょ？
Since when do mad scientists have people skills?
空気読んで どうするのよ
（岡部）なっ うっ
そ… それはだな…
Well, um, you see...
ウフッ
Why are you laughing?
（岡部）なぜ 笑う？
Sometimes you're a good guy, you know?
あんたって たまに
いいやつだから困るのよね
That's the problem.
Now that you understand my greatness, get back to work.
（岡部）
俺の偉大さが分かったら
作業に戻れ
Okay, okay!
はい はい
言っとくけど もう決定だから
Just so we're clear, this is now decided.
I'm going to drag you with me,
whether you want to go or not!
無理矢理でも連れて行くからな
望むところだ
Sounds good to me.
（まゆり）トゥッ トゥルウウ…
うう…
Mayuri?
（店員）あれ？ まゆりちゃん？
（まゆり）ハーッ
どうしたの？ こんな大荷物
What's with all this stuff?
Shouldn't you call that Okarin guy?
オカリンとかいうのを
呼んだほうがいいんじゃないの？
It's okay...
（まゆり）
大丈夫 もう少しなので…
I'm almost there.
ここ見なさいよ！
Look at the label!
It says "Makise" right here!
ちゃんと書いてあるでしょう
“牧瀬”って！
（岡部）
牧瀬プリンと読めるではないか！
It reads "Makise pudding."
That's just a brand name, like Morinaga pudding or Koiwai pudding.
森永(もりなが)さんちのプリンも―
小岩井(こいわい)さんちのプリンも
同じだろう？
Don't play stupid!
ヘリクツを言うな！
Who's "Makise," anyway?
大体 牧瀬とは何者だ？
That's my name!
（紅莉栖）私の名前だ！
"Christina Makise"?
クリスティーナ牧瀬か…
If only you'd written "Christina" instead,
だったら 素直に
クリスティーナと書いておけば―
I wouldn't have accidentally ingested the extra calories.
うっかり ムダなカロリーを
摂取せずに済んだものを…
Don't eat other people's food!
（紅莉栖）
人の物を勝手に食べといて
And that's my spoon! Don't use it!
大体 それ私のスプーンでしょ
勝手に使わないでよ！
You use the lab's forks, don't you?!
（岡部）
貴様も ラボのフォークを
勝手に使っているではないか！
（まゆり）ハア… 到着
I'm here...
ふぃー
ん？ どうしたの それ？
What's all that?
Mayushii's cosplay materials and sleepover set!
（まゆり）
コスの材料と まゆしぃの
お泊まりセットだよー
Sleepover?
（紅莉栖）お泊まり？
Yup!
うん　コミマ用のコスを作るのです
I'm going to make some cosplay outfits for Comima.
Are you sure?
本当に大丈夫なの？ ご両親は？
What about your parents?
I told them about it.
（まゆり）
ちゃんと言ってきたよ
You're staying over too, right?
紅莉栖ちゃんも お泊まりでしょ？
電話レンジの改良で…
To work on the Phone Microwave?
え？ そうね そうしようかと
思っていたけど
Yeah, I thought I might.
But it's kind of depressing to be here.
ただ ここに泊まると
気がめいるのよね
There's this Hououin something guy
鳳凰院なんとかさんが
勝手に人のプリンを食べるから
who goes around eating other people's pudding.
あっ？ 鳳凰院凶真だ
名前ぐらい覚えろ！
It's Hououin Kyouma!
Learn my name, already!
You're the last person I want to hear that from!
（紅莉栖）
あんたに言われたくない
つうかプリンのほうはスルーか！
And don't ignore the part about the pudding!
Maybe I should leave?
（まゆり）
帰ったほうがいいかなあ？
（紅莉栖）えっ？ あ…
私は泊まっても いいけど
No, I'll stay,
but if I do, then Okabe should leave.
だとしたら岡部は
出てったほうが いいわね
（岡部）何だと？
What?!
The lab is the house of my soul!
俺にとって ラボは魂の住処(すみか)！
出ていくなど
I could never leave—
Why is her condition for staying that I go shopping?
（岡部）
なぜ 一緒に泊まる条件が
買い出しに行くことになるのだ
Come to think of it,
考えてみれば 昨日から ずっと
助手のおつかいをしているような…
I've been running errands for my assistant since yesterday.
Christina?
（岡部）クリスティーナか
From: Assistant
Subject: I demand compensation and an apology
I demand two puddings,
as punishment for the one you ate. And...
We're taking a late bus to Aomori,
due to finances.
フッ 何を浮かれている
ラボメンとしての本分を忘れるな
"What are you so happy about?"
"Don't forget your role as a lab member."
I'm not happy, stupid!
浮かれてなんかないわよ バカ！
ほえ？ 何？
What?
（紅莉栖）
あっ ああ… 何でもないわ
早く入っちゃうわよ
It's nothing!
Let's get in, before Okabe gets back.
岡部が戻ってくる前に
Okay.
（まゆり）うん
My assistant again?
また助手か？
You know too much.
You know too much
What?
何だ…
ハッ
出ねえ
ハッ まゆり…
Mayuri...
（男）うわっ
（岡部）ハア ハア まゆり…
Mayuri!
まゆり！
ハア ハア ハア…
（まゆり･紅莉栖）ん？
（紅莉栖）ゆ… ゆ…
I'll never forgive you! Ever!
許さない！
絶対 許さないからな！
Okarin, Mayushii is very sad and very embarrassed.
（まゆり）オカリン…
まゆしぃは とっても悲しいし
恥ずかしいのです
Geez!
ったく！ 風呂場をのぞいた上に
買い出しも全部忘れてきたって？
Not only did you peep on us in the shower, you forgot all the shopping!
ホント 信じらんない
I can't believe it!
ちょっと岡部？
Hey, Okabe!
Okarin?
（まゆり）オカリン？
あっ！ ダル君…
It's Daru!
What's wrong?
（紅莉栖）
どうしたの？ こんな夜に…
Why are you here so late?
（橋田）うん…
I knew it.
やっぱり…
When I accessed it from the outside,
外からパソコン アクセスして
何か変と思ってたんだけど
I thought there was something weird.
Is something wrong?
何かあったの？
The lab is connected directly to the heart of SERN.
（橋田）
今 ここ ＳＥＲＮの中心部と
ダイレクトで回線がつながってる
（岡部）ＳＥＲＮ？
SERN?
You've taken over their system?
システムを掌握したというのか？
I guess so. I win the Internet!
（橋田）まあね キリッ
Or so I'd like to say,
…と言いたいところだけど
実際は なんか分からないうちに
つながっていた
but to be honest, I was connected before I even knew it.
SERN's been standing naked outside my house this whole time.
いつの間にか ＳＥＲＮが勝手に
全裸待機してた的な
ワクテカ？
Say what now?
Wait!
ちょっと待って！
If we're connected without having done anything,
こっちが何もしてないのに
つながっているって…
doesn't that imply that they've found us out
つまり ＳＥＲＮのほうが
こっちの動きに気付いて―
逆にアクセスしてきたって
ことじゃないの？
and are connecting to us?
ハッ
（橋田）
うーん でも バレるような
ヘマはしてないはずだし…
Hmm... But I don't think I've made any errors that would've gotten us caught.
Now we can use the LHC all we want.
（岡部）まさか…
It can't be...
The LHC?
SERN!
ＳＥＲＮ
Okarin?
オカリン？
（紅莉栖）ん？
携帯に何かあったの？
Is something wrong with your phone?
No...
（岡部）いや…
Nothing.
何でもない
～